Crystal, crystal, crystal.
Crystal, I like you, okay?
I didn't say that in that particular situation,
the way I was explaining it with community effect.
I always say the wrong thing.
I'm just saying if I ever did say the wrong thing,
maybe it was a joke, okay?
Not to get so offended, okay, but there but then you respond with like a bunch of hate speech
And I say anything I really don't mind the word, but it is hate speech crystal
I think that is it's hate speech anything and so and I I don't know if you understand like you know
You're not supposed to you know using that kind of like language on my show you know even if it's loud on YouTube
I'm not
It's you know, it's murky, you know might not be specifically that I'd say that but it's like it's one of those, you know, so
And it's just like disrespectful to me like even as a gay person that's like for you know, just to be throwing that word around like in the kind of like
an unkind way
But I know you don't mean it in a bad way
Yeah, she might be you know
You know, you know, because it's like, you know, especially the beautiful women like everyone wants to you know, like I have the beautiful woman on their side and so
But she's on every side, you know
It's watch out for beautiful women guys
Anyway
Yeah, I'll keep I mean it's a Alex
Yeah much you got mental energy, you know, so why I spend my mental energy and especially like on my show. Oh
My god, thank you being paranoid about everybody's face. No, I my paranoia
I've already I've been as paranoid as you can be already in my past. I'm at this point
I'm like I'm way past my life expectancy. Anyway, you're kidding. Oh, it's a mute. Okay. Hold on
Yeah, I'm here
You have to keep I know every possibility, but it's like but Alex if you every possibility
It's like there's a saying it's like keep an open mind, but don't open it so wide that your brains fall out
Okay. Yeah, so I'm trying to say I just want to like
I don't want to put enough. I don't have emotional energy into it. Oh, it was you okay
I don't put emotional energy into that stuff
Especially it's like not but I have enough of my own stuff to worry about them to go in and it's like I also
Empath and so I feel those emotions anyway, so I don't
so, you know, I
Just need to transmute transmute transmute
Light
Then everyone can see
So yeah, okay, so I understand
But we never we'll never know, you know, it's like but there's but there's people that think that their own
You know their own parents are like your secret agents, you know, and that kind of stuff
And it's like, you know
It's probably not sure, you know, so it's like
People can take it too far, right? Hey camera action Bureau. Hey, you're a member thing a thing that is
Big Camera Action Bureau special shout out for being members, you know, I really appreciate, especially this time, you know, because we, you know, a lot of people, like, there was a lot of membership gifted that first month that, you know, expired, and I'm not sure if you would get to membership or you would reduce yours, but I just appreciate you being here. Thank you.
And I will always try to give all the members a special shout out in the chat.
and as well as the mods.
Hey, Jimmy Cavillers, Alex McQueen's a member too.
Hey, Carmen, again, Action Bureau's a member.
And we got, yeah, we got everyone so far.
Oh, Puppy, hey Puppy, how are you?
Seki, you're, I'm Puppy.
I'm pretty, oh, thank you, thank you so much.
Nails and all, you leave me like my nails,
and my nails are, yeah, my nails, I'm sorry.
I did, I was digging through some tobacco this morning, so.
I clean them last night, I swear, I mean they did it for 30s so quickly, but
What's happening? Not much. You know, I just like, I don't know, I wanted, I have to, like, official Marie is, you know,
a great, great girl and it's like, this time I need to be really careful with,
especially since it's like, I just have, I got people blatantly just like trying to break the rules and it's like, that's like, why would they do that?
Unless they either are like incapable of understanding and following rules, which they obviously are because they're like, you know
Out in society running free. Is there a locked up in like, you know
behind like, you know
Bar, you know steel bars and shit, right? So and then
So they're capable of understanding how to like, you know, please
behave or have the perception of behaving
But they want to come on right right in the fucking my living room and shit on the floor. It's like, no
No, you're not gonna do like
So hey Nancy from CalFresh. How are you?
Alex dinner and eat your superstars
from
Casper wins in New York. Yeah
Well, they are superstars they're my they're I'm glad they're on team psyche
But yeah, but and I love I love them and they've they've proven that they
they fuck with me. I mean, they're loyal people. They fuck with me in a good way, you know.
So, I didn't, you know, they're on my, they're on my, my nice list. Hey, Nick.
Because there's a lot of stuff going, because on the other scenes, there's a lot of, there's a lot,
there's a lot of stuff that you don't see on the show that, you know, so,
really, you know, so if people say I'm on all the time, I'm really, I mean, I'm gonna cut down a
Haven't learned a lot a lot of waking hours, but I
Just I was really wanting to get this going a good good good foundation for it going and then
Just see the top right
Good to see you guys
Easy cameras on what's up my mod yeah, yeah make of the mod. Hey, what's up guys?
Yeah, and mods, I'm gonna have like, you know, probably be modding some people. I don't know if any probably not any of you, but
you know anybody that's not really active in the chat or I
Just question my maybe maybe maybe I'll read mob people understanders. I need way less
Managing mods. I just went crazy with the managing month. I don't know. I was just feeling in a generous mood. I guess
Gave the entire
It's a given entire network controls. I'm not talking about
I'm just saying throughout the time I've been on YouTube,
I've let a lot of trolls be maws, and they're my lesson.
How's it going, how's it doing?
So I think Subway's probably not closed.
I think it's closed yet?
Yeah, it's closed now.
So maybe he'll get Taco Bell,
but I'm not really that hungry to talk about it.
Maybe I'll just drink and pass out.
I did get a good sleep this morning though.
How's everyone doing? Yeah, it sucks. I mean shut down streams and then because it's like we hit we hit good crowds going and then it's like
It's fucked it all up started from scratch and we lose people and then
It's been rough to buy a bit. So that's why you know, it's not it's like on a
On a radio show they'll have a seven-second delay or say if someone says the F4 or something could be broadcast nationally
It's a seven seconds delay it's even less seven seconds of what was said before
And so all the people listening to radio here is seven seconds in silence. I
Wish they had had that feature on stream though that'd be it so cool
That I could just push the button and take the person off the panel and then it'd be fine
But they don't have such a feature
They need like some kind of voice verification or something I don't know
But you can't no matter what you can't really prevent somebody from coming on and saying
Anything you can't stop Alexander Alexander
Don't say that
Yeah, we can't you in this is like defendings defending and lovelies like I figure to end it
not talking about
Yeah, I like I'm watching you to guys you have to watch Alex, you know, I
Think he he like I think he found Gotti's wrench. I had it hidden away in the office
you know Alex has he just has a pair he had locked the keys but went in and
And then the wrench was gone from the evidence room and so and then he now he has one
And so guys keep an eye on Alex. Okay. I see what I will I can't I do have the ability to take it back from him
But I'll let him hang on to it until he
Fucks up. Okay. You better not Alex
I think that is...
Oh, that's your line.
I know that...
I think I get...
It triggers my MK Ultra of PTSD when you say that.
I know other people have said that.
That's really annoying.
So, just don't say it.
So, I don't have a flashback.
Okay, thank you.
It's actually a Miley Cyrus song. Well, it's not called Can't Stop, Won't Stop. No, it's okay. I'm half- I'm half-joking, but half-joking.
I'm half-joking. No, but Miley Cyrus does have a song called We Can't Stop. You probably like it. I think you like it.
Oh, it's okay. Alex, you know, don't worry. It's just words. I can deal with my PCSD. Don't worry.
It's just like, sometimes they don't know what, like...
Sometimes you say it reference to yourself like oh no one's gonna control me and I think well
I want you to at least you know respect me on my on my yeah
You know I'm not gonna try to control you or you let you control me, but
You know we have to keep it you know we can like
You can joke around other panels. I want to have a nice conversation with you on mine. I
Want to see the nice Alex?
The other personality go fuck himself. I'm just kidding. I like the other personality too
He just needs to be locked up in the attic once in a while
I'm just kidding guys these are just jokes. Okay, there used to be a rap song
It was I'm here ultra. You can't find you can't find now. I know well it might be
Hello, it's kind of conscious a little content more controversial now
Yeah, I want the nice Alex the good twin because I need the good twin
They keep the bad twin they put away in the basement and you know in the dark
We put soundproof soundproof stuff over and just you know throwing a chicken bone where once in a while
The good Alex come up and then oh, but you know what's gonna happen the bad Alex is gonna like eventually
Like escape and like and re put the good Alex in there and pretend he's a good Alex
Can you imagine him doing that and then I then I have the evil out that I wouldn't even know it
My god, isn't it complicated having the two personalities one body? It really is
It's a nice out. Yeah, can I talk to the get out? It's like when they
People that do multiple personality people they'll talk to me like I talked to they don't have to always have like a child personality
Or these are or alters are called a child. I don't have like an old man
I didn't have all these different personality. Oh, and they'll do voices in this thing. It's like it's really good
I mean if they're not just genuinely like it's transmitting this it's pretty good acting
It's like any different accents and stuff, but I think some people might play up on like the attention
I don't think the local personalities. I don't know how
Unaware of each other personality each personality is I don't think unless you're really fragmented like super fragmented
That would be extreme trauma, but usually
Use the personalities can the different parts you can vibe together
Tranquilizer who needs a tranquilizer me
I'm sure I'm shrink super fragmented right and that's like you know part of the just part of like the
spiritual process and like, you know, we you're shattered all these times in our life
And there's all this all this stuff happens and I say we have a psyche, you know, you know, it's called the psyche actually
No, it's called the soul and it's like
It's kind of like it shatters like it shatters like glass, but it's more of like it's more of like, you know
glass is actually a liquid you know the glass is actually liquid and
So it can like come back to it's like you can heal it's not like
Glass that breaks in a window or a signature place the window you can't replace the soul
It's like you have to I mean go and like find the fragments
in your in the astral in
Different situations in the real world in the self exploration find the fragments and reconcile everything
I think I mean if not everyone can do it. It is
It's like why
You know there's some people that are you if you go to have a surgery you want to have major surgery you go
To like a talented surgeon you don't just don't go to like cousin Jim with that with the hacksaw and say hey
Let's you know take out my whatever now you go to like an experienced surgeon, right? It's like so it's
There's people that have experience in the field that you would want as opposed to like
People that are not
That are not experienced in the field
You don't have a soul Alex. Oh, come on. I think you do you don't have a psyche of me. I'm here. I'm your psyche aren't I?
Up the link. Okay. Yes. I'm sorry. I don't want
Guys, but if you really need to read the myth of cupid and psyche because the myths are like so
Symbolic of like such all these all these psychological things and
Why things are the way just like there's so much that you can uncover and miss and they have such a meaning you sell the head, okay?
So I'm gonna especially recommend to keep it in psyche and because it's a very beautiful story
Yeah
Very beautiful story
That I was really inspired to name the channel on and and also my other business. I named psyche too. I just was
This is just
Just the vibes it
Resonates me. Oh, you thought. Oh, yeah, there's yeah, it's tricks right here. All right, I mean it's rude reason we're here
You're late on my lap
What's up psych I know it's up. Hold on a second
Oh, sorry, God, I didn't mean you, hon.
In the name of the Father, in the name of the Mother, the Spirit, the Son, the Mother,
the Son, the Holy Spirit, the Son, the Holy Spirit, the Son, the Mother, the Son, the
Son, the Holy Spirit, the Son, the Son, the Mother, the Son, the Holy Spirit, the Son,
the Son, the Son, the Son, the Son, the Son, the Son, the Son, the Son, the Son, the Son,
That is right. That's it. That's it is a beautiful language. It really is. I got chills. I'm doing pretty good. How are you tonight?
Not too bad, buddy. Do you have a good night?
Um, it's pretty good. I mean, I just uh, I mean, I mean, I'm a cat in my lap. I can't I can't complain
Yeah, that's the best thing you got going for you right there spirit to santos hasta maria
You think I'm going to let you two assholes come up here?
What's up?
Shut the fuck up!
You think I'm going to let you two assholes continue with your reign of terror?
You think I'm going to let you assholes take his panel down?
You guys made your fucking match!
Shut the fuck up!
What's up?
What's up Wolfie? What's up guys? Let's have a nice conversation.
What's going on?
I've done some idea, man. Shut the fuck up.
You little panel, little brigade. Shut up. Shut up.
You don't fucking preach. Don't fuck up.
Can I see the cat?
Cry, cry.
I like who like you
Exposing you every single day
Exactly who both of you are your full names your adjus is
Is that Rudy? I love that pretty that's the boy. That's the boy, right? Yeah, he's a bit after the other one
Who is my favorite? I fucking love orange cats
And then here's Lola
Let's keep it about cats cuz sooner or later. They're gonna say some TOS shit and they're gonna report you
They're here to take your panel down. They hate gay people
They're Mormon
Boring I've seen the show before
I know it's like a rerun
It's okay. We all know the accusations. I think you know
All right
You're boring, Alex. You're boring move on
well
you know
Talking about cats right now. We're not talking about your boring shit talking about that orange cat right there. You see that
Yeah, let's talk about our orange cat God and
What you see I'm crippling the little cripples now
Just look at the cat, okay
Fuck up 100%
Come in and fuck you shit up